MARINA SHEMESH

054-3477460, MARINA.SHEMESH 1 @GMAIL.COM

Git, Code Pen, LinkedIn, Articles at Medium.com, Heroku

INTRODUCTION

I am an experienced content writer and administrator who has fallen in love with writing code. I recently completed a coding bootcamp at Elevation Academy and is looking now for a position as a junior full stack developer. I have created several web apps using the MEAN Stack, customized various API's to serve data to apps, learned about working with MongoDB and mySQL databases.

PROJECTS

<u>The Home Cook</u> - Completed during a hackathon, the app is a marketplace app where we connect hungry users with stay-at-home cooks. This is a *MEAN-based* app built with *AngularJS* that integrates with the *Google Maps API* to show the location of the cooks.

An algorithm a day - My latest project where I write about JavaScript algorithms.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1/4/2010 TO 31/1/2017 Intelitek (RoboGroup)

Rosh haAyin

CONTENT ADMINISTRATOR AT AN E-LEARNING COMPANY FOCUSSED ON STEM AND ROBOTICS COURSES

- Responsible for keeping content in various content management systems up to date
- Write procedure manuals and in-house teaching material including updating and STEM user manuals
- QA, edit and troubleshoot online content, coordinate with programmers to solve issues

1/3/2015 to 31/12/2016

52Frames.com

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER FOR THE 52FRAMES PHOTOGROUP

- Help to manage and create the weekly albums and emails, welcome new members and troubleshoot various issues
- Co-ordinate with other 52Frames administrators to choose the cover photo and the 2nd and 3rd weekly winners
- Social Media manager including instagram and twitter.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT CODING BOOTCAMP

5/2/2010 TO 10/5/2017

Elevation Academy

Tel Aviv

The last three months I have been intensively studying to program at a coding bootcamp where I learned and made the following:

- Computer science fundamentals such as object oriented programming and data-structures and algorithms
- Version control using git and github
- HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Full-scale web apps using MEAN stack
- mySQL and MongoDB as well as schema design with MongoDB
- Customized various API's to serve data to apps
- Played with ReactJS

MARINA SHEMESH

054-3477460, MARINA.SHEMESH1@GMAIL.COM

Git, Code Pen, LinkedIn, Articles at Medium.com, Heroku

UX/UI DESIGN FOR ONLINE EDUCATION

Workshop at the Information Design faculty of the University of Holon (2012)

YEDA TECHNICAL WRITING COURSE (2009)

BSC DEGREE IN GENETICS FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF PRETORIA, SOUTH AFRICA (1989)

SYSTEMS, PROGRAMS AND APPS THAT I OFTEN WORK WITH:

JavaScript	AngularJS	JQuery	Sublime Text	JIRA	Codepen.io	Confluence	Moodle
MEAN stack	TDD	HTML/CSS	Git Hub	Articulate Storyline	Wordpress	Amazon S3 browser	Corel Paint Shop